You stand before the door,
Wondering what lies beyond the dark frame.

An unseen force opens the door.

The space behind is hidden by fog. 
The only way to find out why the doorway seems 
	so familiar is to walk through.

Hesitation forms chills around your feet.
	Ice forms on your souls
		and crackles it's way up your shoes,
Almost as if reaching for your heart.

In two swift motions you break your legs free and head towards the door.
With each step ice forms, but is broken with a pull.

You smile, laugh and walk through the door.
